empireavenue.com 2010-12-28

# Empire Avenue | Privacy Policy

_This document updated: 25/11/2010_

## Privacy Policy

**Empire Avenue Inc. (Empire Avenue) considers issues relating to your privacy to be a serious matter. As such, Empire Avenue has created and implemented this Privacy Policy so that you understand what Empire Avenue may and may not do with certain Personal Information.**

**This Privacy Policy describes the guidelines Empire Avenue uses to protect the information we collect about you during your visit(s) to the EmpireAvenue.com Web site ( the “Web Site”). By registering on the Web Site you consent to the collection and use of information described below and in theWeb Site Terms and Conditions of Use.**

**This Privacy Policy will apply to all websites of Empire Avenue that link to this Privacy Policy. Information will be shared with other users in accordance with this Policy and yourPrivacy Settings. You are encouraged to review your Privacy Settings on a regular basis to ensure the levels are set appropriately.**

**Collection of Information**

Empire Avenue will collect information of three types about you: (1) Personal Information, (2) Web Site Information, and (3) Third Party Information.

  1. Personal Information refers to information that you provide us directly (i.e. through the forms on the site). This includes but is not limited to your name, photo, your date of birth, your e-mail address, your country, your interests, your profile information etc.
  2. Web Site Information is information that Empire Avenue collects about you during use of the Website. This can be information obtained from posts on your profile pages, your private messaging, and other account activity. It may also be collected about you from the messages and posts and account activity of others regarding you. It also includes information like your browser type and IP address. We may use "cookies" to help us store and collect other information based on your browsing.[1]
  3. When you register as an Registered User, Empire Avenue will enable you to provide us with your login information for various third party sites (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Flickr and your Blog site). Empire Avenue will then access your account and gather all available information from these third party sites as dictated by your Privacy Settings on those sites. This information is called Third Party Information. We will remove this Third Party Information from our system after a certain period of time (currently set at a month).

The information set out in subparagraphs (2) and (3) above will be gathered by an automated system and will not be available to any individual in its original format unless you have given us explicit permission via your Privacy Settings. It will further be processed automatically (as described below) and utilized by Empire Avenue and shared with advertisers in processed form. 

**Children Under Age 13**

Empire Avenue does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register with Empire Avenue or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete any personal information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@empireavenue.com](mailto:privacy@empireavenue.com)

**Internal Use of Information**

When you use Empire Avenue, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as Personal Information, comments, messages, photos, videos, or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the Privacy Settings you select. Information regarding your influence scores and your Empire Avenue virtual stock price may be shared and searchable through your public profile to services and users outside of Empire Avenue. However, the information available on your Empire Avenue public profile can be controlled, or the profile disabled, in your personal Privacy Settings.

All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose Personal Information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, or other items, this information may become publicly available. Such information may be accessed or indexed by third party search engines and as a result remain available on their services even if you change your Settings on Empire Avenue and it is removed from Empire Avenue. Empire Avenue has no control over the use of any information by any outside party that is, or was previously, made available publicly available on Empire Avenue in accordance with your Privacy Settings. This includes any content indexed by internet search engines.

In addition to this, Empire Avenue reserves the right to access, utilize, and reproduce personal information it collects about you, though it will obey any restrictions set up in your Privacy Settings. 

For example, we may distribute your name and profile picture with any posts or private messages that you write on the Web Site. Your name and profile picture may also be used on our “leader boards” and other aspects of our website. You may control, to some extent, the distribution of your name and profile picture through your Privacy Settings.

We may also use your name and contact information to send you notifications regarding changes to our service or new services offered by Empire Avenue that we think you may find valuable.

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email or instant message in your name inviting him or her to visit the site, and may send up to two reminders to them. Empire Avenue stores this information to send invitations and reminders.

**Sharing of Information with Third Parties**

Because of the nature of the Empire Avenue service, it is in the best interest of all involved that we share some information about you with third party advertisers and/or partners. The degree to which this information is shared must be agreed to by you. You have control over the sharing of information via your Privacy Settings. 

As a Registered User, Empire Avenue may use or share your Personal Information and Web Site Information without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating the number of people in a network like a band, movie and personalizing advertisements. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put a favorite movie in your profile, we might serve you an advertisement highlighting a screening of a similar one in your town. But we don't tell the movie company who you are. This information also allows us to extract useful statistics about Registered Users whom you follow or hold shares in. 

The role of a Registered User in the Empire Avenue site is to create a brand that potentially hosts advertising through the Empire Avenue advertising platform. In order to make this advertising as effective as possible (to the benefit of both you as a Registered User and the Advertiser), we will take all three types of information (Personal Information, Web Site Information and Third Party Information) and process them into metrics which we will make available to any interested advertisers. These metrics may include things like your popularity online or your compatibility with certain advertising keywords (how much you talk about food, for example, or sneakers). While we will make commercially reasonable efforts to protect your privacy we do not accept liability whatsoever (including but not limited to special, indirect or consequential damages) if a third party is able to somehow deduce details about you from the general metrics we provide.

Aside from this, we share your site information with third parties only when we believe such sharing 1) will improve your experience with Empire Avenue , 2) is legally required or, 3) is permitted by you. For example: 

  * — We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer.
  * — We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Empire Avenue service or using the Empire Avenue name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.
  * — We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Empire Avenue business, or individual business units owned by Empire Avenue, were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

**Links**

The Web Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Empire Avenue. 

**Changing or Removing Information**

Access and control over your personal information on the Web Site is readily available to you through the profile editing tools. Empire Avenue users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Empire Avenue account may do soon the Settings pages. Removed Personal Information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of Empire Avenue. It may also remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content. Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on the Web Site, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another Web Site user) you generally cannot remove such communications.

**Security**

Empire Avenue takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). ). (To learn more about SSL, go to <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer>). Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of the Empire Avenue Web Site, please contact us through the Help Centre. 

**Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**

Your use of Empire Avenue, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may also contact us at [privacy@empireavenue.com](mailto:privacy@empireavenue.com). 

_This document updated: 04/11/2010_

* * *

[1]A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Empire Avenue. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.
